>> Kyle Simpson: 我们的第一个核心单元是类型系统和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Our first core
unit is the types system and
确切地说，我们如何处理我们要处理的类型，叫做胁迫。
specifically, how we deal with types which
we're gonna get to, it's called coercion.
是你被告知要避免的邪恶的事情
It's that evil thing that you've
been told to avoid and you're gonna
发现我的感觉我认为是你的重要缺失组件
find out from me, that I think it's
a critical missing component in your
您不了解的应用程序，并在代码中使用此应用程序。
applications that you don't understand,
and also utilize this within the code.
所以，要明白，我们其实是要从头开始。
So, to understand it we actually have
to work our way from the beginning.
我们得从地面开始工作
We have to work our way
from the ground up.
所以我们要跳上来谈谈原始的类型。
So we're gonna jump in and
talk about the primitive types.
你们中的许多人可能以前也听到过这种说法。
Many of you have probably
heard this assertion before.
在 JavaScript 中，所有内容都是对象。
In JavaScript everything is an object.
>> Kyle Simpson: 此语句有原因，但
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There is a reason for
this statement, but
这个说法是错误的，这是错误的。
this statement is a misconception,
this is false.
顺便说下这是个笑话
And that's a joke, by the way.
[ LAUGH] ，因为 false 不是对象。
[LAUGH] because false is not an object.
False 是其中一个不是对象的值的示例。
False is an example of one of those
values that is not an object.
人们为什么说一切都是物体的原因
The reason behind why people
say everything is an object,
因为 JavaScript 中的大多数值可以用作对象。
is because most of the values in
JavaScript can behave as objects.
但这并不能使它们成为物体。
But that does not make them objects.
我们一会儿再讨论拳击赛
We'll come back to that when we
talk about boxing a bit later.
所以这不是正确的语句，这不是精确的语句，但是
So this is not a correct statement,
this is not an accurate statement but
这是最普遍的说法
it's one of the most pervasive statements.
我查过了
I did search and
找到了成千上万个这样的例子
found thousands of examples of
people saying things like this.
说他们是权威的，他们写了书，
And saying them authoritatively,
they've wrote books, and
他们写了博客文章他们把名字写在博客上
they wrote blog post, and
they put their name on it.
他们说这是事实，但这并不是幽灵所说的。
And they said this is a fact, and
yet that's not what the specs says.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 有时
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Sometimes,
人们都跟我说什么都不重要
people argue with me that it
doesn't matter what the specs says.
重要的是，在我的代码中它的行为方式。
All that matters is,
how it behaves in my code.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 对我来说，这很像告诉科学家，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To me that's
a lot like telling a scientist,
为什么苹果从树上掉了
it doesn't matter why
the apple fell from the tree.
我们看到它掉到了，这不重要。
We saw it falling, it doesn't matter why.
是的，它确实是这样，它绝对是重要的原因。
Yes it does, it absolutely does,
it absolutely matters why.
那么，如果我们看 JavaScript，就在这个规范的右边
So, if we look at JavaScript,
in this specification right near the very
最重要的是在这个规格之前
top actually, there's not much
before this in the specification,
它会告诉我们有原始的类型
it tells us straight up that
there are primitive types.
好的，你会看到它们在此处列出了未定义的，空的，布尔值，字符串，符号，
Okay, and you'll see them listed here
undefined, null, boolean, strings, symbol,
编号和对象。
number, and object.
它列出了我们所说的原始类型。
It list those out as we
referred to as primitive types.
所以让我们深入了解原始类型，了解它们是什么，
So let's dive in to the primitive types,
to understand what they are and
它们是如何区别的，或者它们是如何区分的，
how they differ or
how they are distinct from,
就是把一切都当作一个物体
just simply referring to
everything as an object.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 第一，有未定义的类型。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Number one,
there is an undefined type.
正如我们所看到的，未定义的类型在其中只有一个值，并且
And as we'll see, the undefined type
has one and only one value in it, and
它是未定义的值。
it is the undefined value.
也有字符串类型。
There's also string type.
这些都是原始的字符串
These are primitive strings,
而不是像 Java那样创建的字符串对象。
not the string object that you
create in something like Java.
这只是双引号或单引号字符串文字，对吗 ?
This is just the double quotes or
the single quotes string literal, right?
这是一个基本字符串。
This is a primitive string.
有一种叫做弦的类型
There's a type called string,
有一个叫号码的类型，指所有 JavaScript 的号码，
there's a type called number,
refers to all of JavaScript's numbers,
虽然那里有个小洞穴我们一会儿就会回来
although there's a little caveat
there we'll come back to in a second.
有一个叫做布尔值的类型，它指的是特定的两个值，
There's a type called boolean,
that refers to the specific two values,
true 和 false。
true and false.
在某些语言中，历史上只有零，
In some languages, in historical
days there was only zeroes and
这些都是真实和虚假的
ones to reference the idea of true and
false.
JavaScript 实际上具有称为 true 和 false的值。
JavaScript actually has
values called true and false.
它们是一种特殊的类型。
And they are a special type.
它们的行为方式与其他类型不同。
And they behave differently,
than this other types.
然后，就有对象类型。
And then, there's the object type.
是的，对象是一种类型。
And yes, the object is a type.
它有很多子类型。
It has many subtypes to it.
我想这就是很多人感到困惑的地方
And I think that's where
a lot of people get confused,
就是因为它们是亚种
is that just because they're subtypes.
或者就因为有个叫拳击的东西
Or just because there
something called boxing,
在某些事物中，事物可以作为一个物体，但这并不是一个物体。
where something can behave as an object,
that doesn't make it an object.
有些东西是物体
There are things that are objects.
这是一些原始类型，在 JavaScript 语言中存在。
So this are some primitive types,
that exist in the JavaScript language.
你说 X 等于 42 ，或者你说 X 等于 42 ，
When you say X equals the number 42,
or you say X equals quotes 42,
你说作为开发者，有不同的意图
you are saying as a developer, there
is a different intent that I have for
我对这个价值的期望
the behavior I expect out of this value.
这就是我们的意思
That's what we mean by a type.
固有特征的集合
The set of intrinsic characteristics,
我们希望能用这个价值来做
that we expect to be able
to do with that value.
因此，如果我们期望与数字的不同，那么我们可以进行算术运算，
So if we expect something different
from numbers we can an arithmetic,
那么我们能用诸如字符之类的字符串来做什么
then what we can do with strings
like accessing characters,
这些是不同的值，我指的是不同的值类型，好吗 ?
those are different values I mean
different values types, okay?
最近几年又加上了几年，
There is also add it recently
a few years back in years six,
较小的类型，但在较小的调用简单的类型上的原语类型，
a lesser none type but the primitives
of types on the less call simple,
符号不用常用于很多白色的
symbols don't get use to
often a lot of white for
基本使用的 JavaScript ，用于创建对象上的专用密钥。
JavaScript that use basically you
create suto private keys on objects.
不是很隐私但有点模糊
Not really private, but kinda obscure.
所以你没看到那些用过很多的，更可能是用在框架上的
So you don't see those used a lot, more
probably used in frameworks than you're
将会看到您的一般 JavaScript 代码，但它是基本类型。
gonna see in your general JavaScript code,
but it is a primitive type nonetheless.
然后我们有其他类型的
And then we have some other types, or
其他可能表现得像我们应该问的类型的东西
other things that may behave like
types that we should ask about.
例如，发生了什么或
For example, what happens or
我们如何处理那些从未被宣布过的事情
how are we dealing with things
that have never been declared?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一种吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Is that a type?
Sorta ，但实际上，该规范并不真正将其定义为一种类型。
Sorta but not really, the spec
doesn't really define it as a type.
但它有它的行为，我们可以期待和理解，
But it has a behavior to it,
that we can expect and understand, and so
如果它有一种行为我们至少可以用引号来说明它是一种类型
if it has a behavior we could sorta at
least with air quotes say it's a type.
>> Kyle Simpson: 关于 Null，我没有把它放在列表中
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What about null,
I didn't put that in the list and
JavaScript 调用类型。
JavaScript calls that a type.
但不在名单里所以为什么会在这里
But it's not in the list,
so why is it over here?
这是因为，它有点讽刺。
Well it's because,
it's a little bit corcky.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这就是直接的历史问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And this is just
straight up, a historical bug and
我们一会儿就知道了
we'll see in just a moment.
>> Kyle Simpson: 功能如何 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And
what about functions though?
JavaScript 甚至不列出函数。
JavaScript didn't even list out function.
如果您仔细查看先前的列表，那么它未列出函数，但是
If you look closely in that previous list,
it didn't list out function and yet
我们可以直观地了解这些函数的函数
we know intuitively,
that values which are functions
具有非常具体的行为，这与以下值的值不同 :
have a very specific behavior, that is
different from values that are numbers for
比如说，比如说，不是一种类型。
say for example, so isn't it a type.
JavaScript 指的是主要作为对象类型的子类型的函数。
JavaScript refers to functions essentially
as a subtype of the object type.
事实上，某些地方把它们称为可调用对象。
In fact, in certain places refers
to them as callable objects.
因此，它是一种类型，但它是子类型，而不是顶级类型。
So, it's sorta a type but
a subtype rather than a top level type.
亚射线我们一直在用这个
Arrays, we use this all the time, and
他们肯定有具体的行为。
it seems like they definitely
have a specific behavior.
他们是按数字编制索引的
They're numerically indexed, and
它们具有自动更新的长度属性。
they have a length property
that automatically updates.
他们有各种各样的方法。
And they have various methods to them.
那么，他们是一种类型吗 ?
So, are they a type?
再说一次最好的思考方式
Again, the best way to think about them,
我所提出的最好的精神模型就是它是对象类型的一个子类型。
the best mental model I've come up with is
that it's a subtype of the object type.
它是这个数字索引的特殊类型的对象。
It's a special kinda object
with this numeric indexing.
有个特别的东西有这个神奇的长度
A special kinda object that has this
magical length property gather thing on
它，好吗 ?
it, okay?
所以它不是一个顶级类型，但它肯定是一种价值。
So it's not really a top level type, but
it's certainly a kinda value that has
某种程度上的行为对我们来说是有用的
a certain kinda behavior, and it's
useful for us to be able to distinguish.
如果我们需要用一个阵列做一些事情，并且我们有这个价值，我们不知道
If we need to do something with an array,
and we have this value we don't know if
它是阵列的我们要确定它是一个阵列吗
it's array,
we need to determine is it an array?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Speaking of determining,
我们要怎么确定这一切
how are we gonna determine
all of this things?
我要投中了一些前瞻性的想法
And I'm gonna throw in,
a little of forward thinking stuff.
因为此刻，这并不是在这个规范中。
Because at the moment,
this isn't actually in the spec.
但这就像是第三阶段
But it's like, stage three and
至少我希望很快就能降落了
probably gonna land in the spec,
at least I hope soon.
最终， JavaScript 得到了巨大的支持， bigint 支持，
And that's finally the JavaScript
getting big and support, bigint support,
大整数支持。
large integer support.
当它进入 JavaScript 的时候，几乎肯定是当它降落的时候
And when it does come to JavaScript,
almost certainly when it lands in
这种语言将会是另一种原始类型
the language,
it's gonna be another primitive type.
所以它就在这个清单上因为它不是在这里
So it's on this list only because,
it's not actually here but
它其实已经在 V8中实施了。
it's actually already implemented for
example in V8.
因此，在所有基于 Chrome 的环境中，包括节点，
So in all of your Chrome based
environments including node,
你有很大的支持
you have big and support.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 很可能在语言中正式地着陆。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And it's likely gonna
land officially, within the language.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 显然有一个警告，直到它在那里，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There is obviously
a caveat that until it's there,
它不在那儿
it's not there.
情况已经很晚了快到第四步了
And things have been,
late stage three almost stage four and
然后被完全删除。
then been completely deleted.
所以我不能保证会有齿龈
So I can't guarantee,
that there will be bigints but
这一点我肯定会说至少百分之九十五
it's pretty certain at this point,
I'd say at least 95%.
所以，有些东西是我们可以预期的一些特点，
So, this are some things that are values
that we can expect certain characteristics
有个很重要的细节我不想你错过这里
from, and there's a critical detail
that I don't want you to miss here,
这大部分都不是物体对吧
which is that most of this
are not objects, right?
这是对象，所有这些不是对象。
This are objects, all of this not objects.
所有这些可能具有或至少有多个可能具有类似对象的对象。
All of this may have or at least
many of these may have object like
您可以选择的行为，但它们绝对不是对象。
behaviors that you can opt into, but
they are definitely not objects.
与 C + plus 和 Java等语言不同，在 JavaScript 和
Unlike languages like C plus plus and
Java, in JavaScript and
在其他动态类型语言中，它不是具有类型的变量。
in other dynamically typed languages,
it is not the variables that have types.
这是具有类型的值本身。
It is the values themselves
that have types.
这与我刚刚给出的本能定义相符
And that matches with that instinctual
definition I just gave types
他们认为我们从价值观中所期望的或本能的特征
that they assumed or instinctual
characteristics we expect from the values.
好吧当然
Well, of course.
让我们将它们称为值类型。
Let's refer to them as value types.
那是区分它的好方法
That's a better way of
distinguishing it than to try to get
这些类型的警察都跳下来告诉我们，这不符合资格
the types policed to jump all over us and
tell us, no this don't qualify as types.
我已经有过这种事了
I've had that happen.
我已经有很多时间了好吗
I've had that argument many of time, okay?
就我而言，如果 JavaScript 称它是一种类型，我认为它是一种类型。
As far as I'm concern, if JavaScript
calls it a type, I think it's a type.